// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "find the co factor of the elements 2 and -5  ",
    answer: "17,3",
    options: [
      "17,3",
      "11,3",
      "10,5",
      "16,2 "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If 3x/(x-6)(x+a)=2/x-6 + 1/x+a then a= ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "2",
      "12",
      "3",
      "13"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Δabc,if a/b^2-c^2 + c/b^2-a^2=0 then B=",
    answer: "π/3",
    options: [
      "π/2",
      "π/4",
      "2π/3",
      "π/3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "sinh^-1[x/√1-x^2]=?",
    answer: "tanh^-1 x",
    options: [
      "coth^-1 x",
      "sinh^-1 x",
      "-tanh^-1 x",
      "tanh^-1 x"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If tan^-1 3+tan^-1 x=tan^-18 then x=",
    answer: "1/5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "1/5",
      "15/14",
      "14/5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "If tanθ+secθ=√ 3 then the principal value of θ+π/6 is ",
    answer: "π/3",
    options: [
      "π/4",
      "π/3",
      "2π/3",
      "π3/4"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 7,
    question: "cos7A/secA - sec7A/cosecA=?",
    answer: "cos8A",
    options: [
      "tan2A",
      "cos8A",
      "secA",
      "cos6A"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "real part of a+ib/a-ib is.....",
    answer: "a^2-b^2/a^2+b^2",
    options: [
      "2ab/a^2+b^2",
      "a^2-b^2/a^2+b^2",
      "a^2+b^2/a^2-b^2",
      "2ab/a^2-b^2"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "θ is an acute angle between lines y=2x+3,y=x+1 then the value of θ is=?",
    answer: "1/3",
    options: [
      "π/2",
      "4/1",
      "1/2",
      "1/3"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 10,
    question: "if y=log(1+x)-2x/1+x then y is increasing on the interval",
    answer: "(1,∞)",
    options: [
      "(-∞,1)",
      "(1,∞)",
      "(2,∞)",
      "(-∞,0)"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "the derivative of (sin^2 (2x+3))",
    answer: "2sin(4x+6)",
    options: [
      "2sin(4x+6)",
      "2sin(x+1)",
      "2sin(2x+3)",
      "2sin(x+3)"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "If (x+3) and (3,5) are extremites of a circle with center at (2,y) then the value of x and y is  ",
    answer: "1,4",
    options: [
      "1,4",
      "2,4",
      "5,2",
      "1,2"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 13,
    question: "find the eccentricity of hyberbola 9y^2 -4x^ 2=36",
    answer: "√ 13/2",
    options: [
      "13/2",
      "√ 13/2",
      "2/13",
      "13/4"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "the length of the subnormal to the parabola y^2=4ax at any print is equal to ",
    answer: "2a",
    options: [
      "√ 2a",
      "a/2",
      "2√ 2a",
      "2a"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "x= asec^3θ and y=atan^3θ then dy/dx=",
    answer: "cotθ/2",
    options: [
      "cot2",
      "tanθ/2",
      "cotθ/2",
      "cotθ"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "∫e2logsecx dx=.......",
    answer: "none of these",
    options: [
      "secxtanx",
      "cosecx",
      "log(secx+tanx)",
      "none of these"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "the area in Square units bounded by the curve y=x^3 ,y=x^2 and the ordinates x=1,x=2 is .....",
    answer: "17/12",
    options: [
      "17/12",
      "12/13",
      "2/7",
      "7/2"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "the differential equation y=Sinnx=bcosnx as a solutions ",
    answer: "d^2 y/dx^2+n^2 y=0",
    options: [
      "d^2 y/dx^2-ny=0",
      "d^2 y/dx^2+n^2 y=0",
      "d^2 y/dx^2+ny=0",
      "d^2 y/dx^2-n^2 y=0"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "lt x^ax -1/e^b -1 x->0 =?	",
    answer: "a/b",
    options: [
      "ab/a",
      "b/a",
      "a/b",
      "ba/b"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "tan^-1 x+tan^-1 y=c is the genral solution of ",
    answer: "dy/dx+1+Y^2/1+x^2=0",
    options: [
      "dy/dx=√1-x^2/1-y^2",
      "dy/dx=1+y^2/1+x^2",
      "dy/dx+1+Y^2/1+x^2=0",
      "none"
    ]
  },
];
